brandinst.com 2017-10-09

# Untitled Document

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Brand Institute and its subsidiary Drug Safety Institute (collectively referred to as “Brand Institute”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from customers, clients and survey takers (“Clients”) of [Brand Institute](http://www.brandinstitute.com/).

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Clients in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Clients contract with Brand Institute for services, when Clients visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Clients may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Clients may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Clients only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Clients may refuse to supply personal identification information with the understanding that such refusal may impact Clients contractual relationship with Brand Institute.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Clients whenever they interact with our Brand Institute or our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Clients’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance Client experience. Clients’ web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Clients may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Brand Institute may collect and use Clients personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize Client experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Clients as a group use the services and resources provided by our company and on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To process payments_  
We may use the information Clients provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Clients information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send Clients information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If Clients decide to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time Clients would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

**_We do not sell, trade, or rent Clients’ personal identification information to others._**   
We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Clients with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

**_Clients and Site visitors may request that their personal identification information not be shared with third parties._**     

**NOTE** : You have the right to access, correct or delete your Personal Data  
**_If Brand Institute were to share personal information with third parties Brand Institute is responsible for ensuring those third parties uphold Privacy Shield principles._**  

**_Brand Institute may share personal information if required to do so in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements_**

 _  
_

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Brand Institute has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Clients to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By contracting for services with Brand Institute or using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site and Brand Institute services following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

**Access to your information**   

Clients may access personal identification information, on request, to ensure its accuracy.  

**Privacy Shield**  

**_Brand Institute is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC)._**  
Brand Institute complies with the U.S.-EU Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries.  Brand Institute has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view Brand Institute’s certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/> ****  

**Dispute Resolution**  

Any information privacy disputes may be filed as a complaint with JAMS at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>   
**_If neither Brand Institute nor JAMS Privacy Shield Program resolves your complaint, you may have the possibility to engage in binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission._**  

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Brand Institute commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. 

Individuals in the European Union with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Brand Institute at:   
[admin_dept@brandinstitute.com](mailto:admin_dept@brandinstitute.com) re: Privacy Shield Dispute  

Brand Institute has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS Privacy Shield Program, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact or visit the JAMS website at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield> for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site and Brand Institute, or your dealings with this Site and Brand Institute, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer Andrew Heck at:

Brand Institute, Inc.  
200 SE 1st St 12th Floor  
Miami, FL 33131    
P: 305 374 2500    
F: 305 374 2504                                      

This document was last updated on September 6, 2016
